Guide to the Leslie Cagan Papers TAM.138
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Subject Files Accessioned 1993-2014
  - Cuba Information Project: Providence, Rhode Island, Undated (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Cuba Information Project: Texas, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Cuba Information Project: Oklahoma, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Cuba Information Project: Oregon, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Cuba Information Project: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1993-1996 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Cuba Information Project: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1993-1996 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Cuba Information Project: Salt Lake City, Utah, Undated (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Cuba Information Project: Will Eickholt, Washington, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Cuba Information Project: Seattle, Washington, 1994-1996 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Cuba Information Project: Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1991; undated (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Cuba Information Project: "Sisters to the Rescue"/Global Exchange, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Cuba Information Project: Global Exchange, 1991-1996 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Cuba Information Project: Ad Hoc Committee and Travel Exchange, 1993-1996 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cuban Youth Speaking Tour, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cuban Youth Lectures Committee, 1994-1996 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cuban Video Project, Undated (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - Cuba Information Project: Center for Cuban Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cambio Cubano, Undated (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - Cuba Information Project: CISPES, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - Cuba Information Project: Committee for International Human Rights Inquiry, Undated (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Cuba Information Project: Crossroads Ministries; Emily Thomas, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cuba Poster Project; Inkworks, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cuban American Alliance Education Fund: Delvis Fernandez, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 56)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cuban American Defense League, Undated (Box 27, Folder 57)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cuban American National Alliance: Luis Martin, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 58)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cuban Committee for Democracy, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 59)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cuban Psychologists Fund: Ethel Tobach, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 60)
  - Cuba Information Project: Washington, DC, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 61)
  - Cuba Information Project: Newark, Deleware, 1991-1995 (Box 27, Folder 62)
  - Cuba Information Project: Florida, 1994-1996 (Box 27, Folder 63)
  - Cuba Information Project: Atlanta, Georgia, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 64)
  - Cuba Information Project: Honolulu, Hawaii, 1991-1994 (Box 27, Folder 65)
  - Cuba Information Project: Chicago, Illinois, 1991-1993 (Box 27, Folder 66)
  - Cuba Information Project: Rockford, Illinois, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 67)
  - Cuba Information Project: Iowa, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 68)
  - Cuba Information Project: Louisiana, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 69)
  - Cuba Information Project: American Friends Service Committee, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 70)
  - Cuba Information Project: American Business Council on Cuba, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 71)
  - Cuba Information Project: General, 1990s (Box 27, Folder 72)
  - Cuba Information Project: Information on Clinton Administration, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Cuba Information Project: Correspondence with Clinton Administration, 1992-1996 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Cuba Information Project: Correspondence with Members of US Congress, 1993-1996 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Cuba Information Project: Legislative Contact, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Cuba Information Project: Information about US Congress, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Cuba Information Project: February 1996 Plane Shootdown: Movement Responses and Action (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Cuba Information Project: February 1996 Plane Shootdown: Information from Cuba and Translations (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Cuba Information Project: February 1996 Plane Shootdown: Newspaper Clippings (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Cuba Information Project: August-September 1994 Immigration Crisis: Newspaper Clippings (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Cuba Information Project: New York Times Clippings, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Cuba Information Project: Trips: Advertising, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Cuba Information Project: Trips: Advertising, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Cuba Information Project: Trips: Second Letter after Deposit, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Cuba Information Project: Trips: Initial Letter and Application, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Cuba Information Project: Trips: Correspondence, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Cuba Information Project: Trips: Notes, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Cuba Information Project: Travel: Efforts to Secure Travel Rights, 1994-1997 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Cuba Information Project: Travel: General, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cuba Delegations, Undated (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Cuba Information Project: Journalist Delegations, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Cuba Information Project: International Solidarity Conference: Contact with Cubans, US Action Proposal, Conference Schedule, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Cuba Information Project: International Solidarity Conference: Logistics, Finances, Lists, National Network on Cuba Task Force, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Cuba Information Project: International Solidarity Conference: Final Documents, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Cuba Information Project: International Solidarity Conference: Outreach and Materials for Participants, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Cuba Information Project: Lesbian/Gay Group: Speaking Tour, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Cuba Information Project: Lesbian/Gay Delegation, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Cuba Information Project: Lesbians/Gays and Cuba, 1992-1995 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Cuba Information Project: Aids Project, 1992-1996 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Cuba Information Project: Funding Exchange, 1990-1996 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Cuba Information Project: Astraea Proposal, 1992-1996 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Cuba Information Project: Thank-you Letters, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Cuba Information Project: Robert Robaina Event, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Cuba Information Project: Fundraising Efforts, 1991-1993 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Cuba Information Project: Funding Proposals and Budgets, 1990-1996 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Cuba Information Project: Donors: Boehm Foundation, 1992; 1996 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Cuba Information Project: Donors: Hilda Diaz, 1990-1992 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Cuba Information Project: Donors: Other, 1991-1996 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Cuba Information Project: Donors: Resist, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Cuba Information Project: Donors: World Fellowship, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Cuba Information Project: Wings of the World, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Cuba Information Project: Human Friendship and Dignity Bonds for Cuba, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Cuba Information Project: Peoples Fast for Peace and Justice in the Americas, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Cuba Information Project: Pledge of Resistance, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Cuba Information Project: Film Project on First Venceremos Brigade: Includes List of Brigade Members, Undated (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Cuba Information Project: Religious Groups, 1991-1995 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Cuba Information Project: MTV Request for Interview with Fidel Castro, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Cuba Information Project: New York City Cuba Coalition, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Cuba Information Project: Target 96: Florida and New Jersey, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cigar Event, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - Cuba Information Project: Correspondence: General, 1993-1995 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - Cuba Information Project: Work Plans, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - Cuba Information Project: InterAction Working Group on Cuba, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - Cuba Information Project: Latin America Working Group, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - Cuba Information Project: Lobby Week, Nov 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cuba Action Newsletter, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Cuba Information Project: Evenson Legal Memorandum on Torricelli Bill, Mar 1992 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Cuba Information Project: Congressional Push, Apr 1992 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Cuba Information Project: Washington, DC Lobby Day, Feb 1993 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Cuba Information Project: Regional Demonstrations, Oct 1995 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Cuba Information Project: October 21, 1995 Demonstration: Finances, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Cuba Information Project: Northeast Regional Work for October 21, 1995 Demonstration (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Cuba Information Project: US House of Representatives Foreign Affairs Committee: Testimony at Hearing, Mar 1992 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Cuba Information Project: Lobby Reports and Correspondence with Members of US Congress, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Cuba Information Project: Lobby Packets, Nov 1991 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Cuba Information Project: Lobby Packets, Jul 1993 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Cuba Information Project: Washington, DC Strategy Meetings, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Cuba Information Project: Legislative Updates, 1991-1996 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Cuba Information Project: Rangel Hearing Testimony, Mar 1994 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Cuba Information Project: Lobby Day, Jun 1994 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Cuba Information Project: National Public Education Day, Jun 1994 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cuba Roundtable, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Cuba Information Project: Wayne Smith Travel Challenge, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Cuba Information Project: Second Leadership Summit, Feb 1994 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Cuba Information Project: Rangel Bill, 1993-1995 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Cuba Information Project: Outreach for October 21, 1995 Demonstration (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Cuba Information Project: Media for October 21, 1995 Demonstration (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Cuba Information Project: Movimiento Por la Paz, 1992-1994 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Cuba Information Project: Clinton Announcement on Travel to Cuba, Oct 1995 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Cuba Information Project: Congressional Action (Torricelli), 1992 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Cuba Information Project: Katie Donahue Memos, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Cuba Information Project: Helms-Burton Act: Actions and Updates, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Cuba Information Project: Helms Bill: Bill and Analysis, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Cuba Information Project: Simon Legislation, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Cuba Information Project: Serrano Bill, 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Cuba Information Project: Nadler Bill, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Cuba Information Project: International Conference in Mexico City, Jun 1992 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Cuba Information Project: Mexico/Va Por Cuba, 1993-1994 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Cuba Information Project: LA Solidarity Meeting in Cuba (April 1993) and First International Conference in Mexico (February 1993) (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Cuba Information Project: Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, 1991-1996 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Cuba Information Project: "Goods for Cuba": Victoria, British Columbia, Canada, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Cuba Information Project: International Lists, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Cuba Information Project: International Support, 1991-1993 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Cuba Information Project: Congress: Legislation, 1993-1995 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Cuba Information Project: Mailings, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Cuba Information Project: Mailings, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Cuba Information Project: Mailings, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Cuba Information Project: Mailing, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Cuba Information Project: Mailings, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Cuba Information Project: Mailing, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Cuba Information Project: Articles on AIDS, 1990-1993 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cuba Letter: Outreach and Finances, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Cuba Information Project: Mailings, 1996-1997 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Cuba Information Project: Mailings, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Cuba Information Project: AIDS and Health Care, 1991-1994 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Cuba Information Project: Visit of HIV-Positive Cubans, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Cuba Information Project: Juan Carlos de la Concepcion Raxach and Raul Llanos Trip to NYC and Public Event, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Cuba Information Project: HIV/AIDS Conference, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Cuba Information Project: AIDS Conference and Brochure, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Cuba Information Project: HIV/AIDS Conference, Havana, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Cuba Information Project: Elena Schwolsky-Fitch and Funding for the AIDS Education Project in Cuba, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cuba AIDS Project, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cuba Letter, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Cuba Information Project: Human Rights Issue, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Cuba Information Project: Powdered Milk Delivery, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Cuba Information Project: Habitat for Humanity, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Cuba Information Project: Environmental Issues, 1992-1995 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Cuba Information Project: Correspondence: General, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Cuba Information Project: Canadian-Cuban Friendship Association, 1992-1994 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Postcards, 1991 / undated (Box 30, Folder 25A)
  - Cuba Information Project: Ocean Press, 1992-1994 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Cuba Information Project: Correspondence about Cruel and Unusual Punishment: The US Blockade Against Cuba, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Cuba Information Project: Solidarity with Cuba Meeting (contains photographs), 1993 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Cuba Information Project: Susan Suchman Slide Show on Cuban Women, Undated (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Cuba Information Project: T.V. Martí, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Cuba Information Project: Alarcon Pamphlet, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Cuba Information Project: Organizers Packet, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Cuba Information Project: Organizers Packet, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Cuba Information Project: Juan Antonio Blanco and Maria del Pilar Diaz-Castanon NYC Speaking Engagement, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Cuba Information Project: Gail Reed Tour, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Cuba Information Project: Gail Reed Tour, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Cuba Information Project: Gail Reed: Promotional Material, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Cuba Information Project: Elsa Agramonte Tour (Visa Denied), 1993 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Cuba Information Project: Federacion de Mujeres Cubanas, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Cuba Information Project: UJC [?], 1995 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Cuba Information Project: Leaflets and Endorsements from Other Cities and Different Organizations, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Cuba Information Project: Fidel Castro's Visit to NYC: Media, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Cuba Information Project: October 21st Cuba Coalition: Logistics, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Cuba Information Project: October 21st Cuba Coalition: Program, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Cuba Information Project: UN Human Rights in Cuba Report, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 44A)
  - Mobilization for Survival (MFS): Affiliate Mailings, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - MFS: Affiliates, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - MFS: Internal Documents, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - MFS: Internal Documents, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - MFS: Internal Documents, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - MFS: Peter Bynum/Direct Mail, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - MFS: Coordinating Committee and Staff: Mailings, Memos, Meetings, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - MFS: Coordinating Committee and Staff: Mailings, Memos, Meetings, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Cuba Information Project: Good Neighbor Relief, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Cuba Information Project: Friendshipment IV and V, 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Cuba Information Project: June 17, 1995 Demonstration in Washington, DC (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Cuba Information Project: Pastors for Peace Sixth Caravan: Hunger Strike, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Cuba Information Project: IFCO/Cuba Conference, NYC, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Cuba Information Project: Friendshipment, NYC, 1992-1994 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Cuba Information Project: Medicines Trip (Pastors for Peace), 1993 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cuba Study Guide, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Cuba Information Project: November 12, 1994 Demonstration (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Cuba Information Project: Friendshipment: National, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Cuba Information Project: Friendshipment, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Cuba Information Project: Friendshipment, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Cuba Information Project: The Crisis, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Cuba Information Project: Boats, Riot, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Cuba Information Project: September 2 and 8 Demonstrations, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Cuba Information Project: United Nations, 1991-1996 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Cuba Information Project: United Nations, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Cuba Information Project: United Nations: Organizing Projects, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Cuba Information Project: Storm: Relief Efforts, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Cuba Information Project: Richard Keating: Storm Video Project, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - National Campaign for Peace in the Middle East (NCPME): Greenpeace, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - NCPME: Minnesota Librarians for Peace and Justice, Minnesota Library Association Social Responsibilities Roundtable, Sanford Berman, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - NCPME: Gulf Peace Team, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - NCPME: Impact Visuals, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - NCPME: International Physicians for the Prevention of Nuclear War, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - NCPME: North American Coalition for Human Rights in Korea, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - NCPME: New Jewish Agenda, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - NCPME: North American Coordinating Committee for Non-Governmental Organizations on the Question of Palestine, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - NCPME: Palestine Human Rights Information Center, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - NCPME: Peace Dividend (Jonathan Feldman), 1990 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - NCPME: Psychologists for Social Responsibility, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - NCPME: Sojourners, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - NCPME: Montgomery, Alabama, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - NCPME: Arizona: General, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - NCPME: Berkeley, California, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - NCPME: Chico, California, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - NCPME: Los Angeles, California, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - NCPME: Marin, California, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - NCPME: Mariposa, California, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - NCPME: Oakland, California, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - NCPME: Sacramento, California, 1990; undated (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - NCPME: San Diego, California, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - NCPME: San Francisco, California, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - NCPME: Walnut Creek, California, Undated (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - NCPME: Toronto, Canada, Undated (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - NCPME: Boulder, Colorado, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - NCPME: Denver, Colorado, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - NCPME: Durango, Colorado, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - NCPME: Fort Collins, Colorado, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - NCPME: Connecticut: General, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - NCPME: Guilford, Connecticut, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - NCPME: Hartford, Connecticut, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - NCPME: New Haven, Connecticut, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - NCPME: Westport, Connecticut, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - NCPME: Washington, DC, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - NCPME: Florida: General, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - NCPME: Jacksonville, Florida, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - NCPME: Orlando, Florida, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - NCPME: Plantation, Florida, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - NCPME: Shalimar, Florida, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - NCPME: Tallahassee, Florida, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - NCPME: Lake Wales, Florida, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - NCPME: Miami, Florida, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - NCPME: Palm Beach, Florida, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - NCPME: Champaign, Illinois, Undated (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - NCPME: Chicago, Illinois, Undated (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - NCPME: Oak Park, Illinois, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - NCPME: Rockford, Illinois, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 48)
  - NCPME: Indianapolis, Indiana, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 49)
  - NCPME: Ames, Iowa, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 50)
  - NCPME: Kansas: General, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 51)
  - NCPME: Lexington, Kentucky, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 52)
  - NCPME: Louisville, Kentucky, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 53)
  - NCPME: Maine: General, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 54)
  - NCPME: Bowie, Maryland, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 55)
  - NCPME: Baltimore, Maryland, Undated (Box 32, Folder 56)
  - NCPME: College Park, Maryland, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 57)
  - NCPME: Hyattsville, Maryland, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 58)
  - NCPME: Boston, Massachusetts, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 59)
  - NCPME: Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 60)
  - NCPME: Huntington, Massachusetts, Undated (Box 32, Folder 61)
  - NCPME: Leverett, Massachusetts, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 62)
  - NCPME: Northampton, Massachusetts, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 63)
  - NCPME: Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 64)
  - NCPME: Detroit, Michigan, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 65)
  - NCPME: East Jordan, Michigan, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 66)
  - NCPME: Novi, Michigan, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 67)
  - NCPME: Traverse City, Michigan, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 68)
  - NCPME: Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 69)
  - NCPME: Rochester, Minnesota, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 70)
  - NCPME: St. Louis, Missouri, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 71)
  - NCPME: Omaha, Nebraska, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 72)
  - NCPME: Asheville, North Carolina, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 73)
  - NCPME: Boone, North Carolina, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 74)
  - NCPME: Chapel Hill, North Carolina, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 75)
  - NCPME: Charlotte, North Carolina, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 76)
  - NCPME: Durham, North Carolina, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 77)
  - NCPME: Raleigh, North Carolina, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 78)
  - NCPME: New Hampshire: General, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 79)
  - NCPME: Bergen County, New Jersey, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 80)
  - NCPME: Moorestown, New Jersey, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 81)
  - NCPME: Montclair, New Jersey, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 82)
  - NCPME: Jersey City, New Jersey, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 83)
  - NCPME: Princeton, New Jersey, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 84)
  - NCPME: Rutgers University, New Jersey, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 85)
  - NCPME: Towaco, New Jersey, Undated (Box 32, Folder 86)
  - NCPME: Santa Fe, New Mexico, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 87)
  - NCPME: New York: General, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 88)
  - NCPME: Buffalo, New York, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 89)
  - NCPME: Ithaca, New York, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 90)
  - NCPME: Long Island, New York, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 91)
  - NCPME: New York City, New York, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 92)
  - NCPME: Rochester, New York, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 93)
  - NCPME: Westchester, New York, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 94)
  - NCPME: Ohio: General, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 95)
  - NCPME: Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 96)
  - NCPME: Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 97)
  - NCPME: Eugene, Oregon, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 98)
  - NCPME: Portland, Oregon, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 99)